never.no 2017-12-16

# never.no | Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Last updated: March 14, 2016

never.no ("us", "we", or "our") licenses software that supports our partners in producing Social TV and Social Advertising solutions. This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when our partners use our software.

Our software uses information sources that are either public and accessible for everyone or have been licensed to us by the social networks themselves. Public sources are websites and APIs that anyone can visit, e.g. www.twitter.com, www.facebook.com or www.instagram.com. Private sources are official APIs created and supported by social networks and these are subject to local and global privacy laws.

Our software collects social content to publish an aggregate or a selection online, in a broadcast production, on a second screen or in an advertisement. As part of the collected data collection, social networks send public profile information of the owner of each post, such as the alias, avatar and real name. Our software does not share this public profile information with any 3rd parties except for licensed users of the software where content is used for display or expressly promoted interaction campaigns. Your content may be used as part of brand marketing campaigns where your explicit permission will be required either as part of the campaign or by direct request.

We, our partners or any third party that’s hired on either’s behalf, do not have access to private profile information such as email addresses, physical addresses, date of birth, professional information, family or non-public communication with others.

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
